When it's all on the line, hold on tight.
Sidelined 2: Intercepted is a romance, comedy film directed by Justin Wu.
Freshman star quarterback Drayton struggles with the weight of expectations after a devastating
setback, while dancer Dallas begins to question the future she thought she wanted.
As their high school relationship begins to unravel under the pressures of distance and self-discovery,
they’ll learn that the bravest versions of themselves emerge when they let life redirect them.
Drayton Lahey, played by Noah Beck.
Dallas Bryan, played by Siena Agudong.
Skyler, played by Charlie Gillespie.
Nathan Bryan, played by Drew Ray Tanner.
Leroy Lahey, played by James Van Der Beek.
Charlotte, played by Roan Curtis.
The 2025 Miami Hurricanes football team represented the University of Miami in the Atlantic
Coast Conference (ACC) during the 2025 NCAA Division I FBS football season.
The Hurricanes were led by Mario Cristobal in his fourth year as head coach.
Their home games were played at Hard Rock Stadium
located in Miami Gardens, Florida.
This season marked the 100th anniversary of Miami Hurricanes football.
Led by former Georgia quarterback Carson Beck, the team started
5–0 for the second consecutive year and ranked No.
2 in the polls before being upset by Louisville.
After a 26–20 overtime loss to SMU, which fell the Hurricanes down to No.
18 in the polls, they closed the regular season with four consecutive wins.
The team finished with a 10–2 regular season record, and 6–2 in ACC
play, finishing second in a five-way tie for No.
2 in the ACC, only behind the eventual ACC champion Duke.
They were selected for the 2025–26 College Football
Playoff and were selected as the No.
10 seed in the final rankings.
Miami started their playoff run by defeating No.
7 Texas A&M 10–3, aided with a game-ending interception from Bryce Fitzgerald.
Then, they upset the defending national champions, the Ohio State Buckeyes
at the Cotton Bowl, as a 9.5-point underdog, winning 24–14.
This was Miami’s first victory in a major bowl game since the 2004 Orange Bowl.
They then advanced to the Fiesta Bowl against Ole Miss, where they won 31–27, thanks to
Carson Beck's 3-yard touchdown scramble in the waning moments of the game.
Miami advanced to the College Football Playoff National Championship against Indiana,
where they lost in their first championship appearance since the 2002 season.
Miami was the first team to play for the national championship in their home stadium since they themselves did it during the 1995
Orange Bowl, and the first since the creation of the national championship game as a game separated from the bowl system.
The film explores themes of dancer, based on novel or
book, college, sequel, teenage romance.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.